

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

# CHAD GIBBONS

## **GET IN CONTACT**

Mobile: +31657532399 julia.lapina@nike.com

#### Website

https://avilaweb.github.io/Julia.git hub.io/

## **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Highly motivated, creative and versatile professional with a growth mindset and high learning agility. Nearly 8 years of experience in project coordinator/producer roles in large–scale projects for international brands such as VISA, Lexus, MINI, Beluga, Metropol. A talent for complex administrative support, strong in analyzing and solving problems. Proven experience in multi-tasking environment, stakeholder management, event management & facilitation.

Cheerful & enthusiastic co-worker with positive energy and a can-do attitude.

# **LANGUAGES**

- English Fluent
- Russian Native
- German Intermediate
- Dutch Beginner

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### NIKE

- Admin Assistant to HRBP's (10.2019 present)
- Admin Assistant to HRBP's (02.2018 06.2018)
- Legal/CAO Executive Assistant (07.2017 01.2018)
- Legal, Security & Brand Protection Assistant (11.2016 05.2017)

#### **MARKA**

- Project manager/coordinator (04.2013 07.2016)
- Project manager in the Business Development Department (01.2012 04.2013)

#### **BNP Paribas**

- Assistant to Member of the Board & Team Assistant to the Trade Finance Department (04.2010 – 11.2011)
- Assistant to Event Manager& Assistant to the Administrative Department (09.2008 – 04.2010)
- Trainee at Client Services Division (07.2008 09.2008)

#### Inline Group

 Assistant to Director in the Power System Department (11.2006 – 01.2008)

# **EDUCATION HISTORY**

### THE STATE UNIVERSITY OF MANAGEMENT.

Master's degree, Crisis Management, Diploma with honors. (2003 - 2008)

#### **HOBBIES**

Running and part of the NRC member, regular participant of charity marathons. TCS Amsterdam marathon, Zandvoort circuit run.

Yoga. Events. Projects around the world. Cooking. Literature. Sightseeing.

## **REFERENCES**

- > Erik van den Hout, SR. HRBP GOT/CF
- > Louise Brix, SR DIRECTOR HR DELIVERY OPS EMEA
- > Bill Berner, NIKE EUROPE GENERAL COUNSEL
- > Frederik Versteeg, NIKE MANAGING ATTORNEY, BRAND SERVICES & COMPLIANCE
- > Yoram Shemtov, NIKE SECURITY DIRECTOR EMEA

#### **PROJECTS**

- Facilitator for a number of HR Café meeting online webinars for circa 200 people.
- Stretch assignment in Data team, coordination, and first point of contact for CDA project team.
- Team event at the museum in Amsterdam for HR team (15 team members), including planning,
- · budgeting, timely status reports.
- Presentation for the Town Hall session for Global Legal team (Art, Inspiration & Sport).
- Offsite for Nike Legal team (50 team members), including transportation, program development,
- budget management.
- Successful arrangement and coordination of 3 events for Brand Protection team (WHQ, EHQ).
- Arrangement and coordination of the Security leadership team trip to Russia, including
- Coordination of the meetings with local security companies and Nike Moscow Team, translation of
- documents related to the WC2018 project.
- Arrangement and coordination of the leadership team trip to Nike office in Italy, including
- Coordination of the meetings with local companies.
- Security brief for Sport Marketing team on WC18.
- "Night of Art" and "Museum Night" art events with the support of the Department of Culture
- of Moscow. Producer for 6 art venues, incl. special assistance to VISA Partnership events (ca
- 3000-6000 visitors in total) (2013, 2015, 2016).
- "Visa Art Weekend". Producer of events for VISA premium cardholders at the main Russian art
- venues (ca 1000 visitors per event) (4–5 times a year: 2014, 2015, 2016).
- Lexus Hybrid Art exhibition. Project coordinator for one of the leading contemporary art
- exhibitions in Russia (2015, 2014, 2013).
- Event manager for 5 private events, 6 corporate events (also for Gazprom subsidiary), 8
- weddings (2011-2014).
- Project coordinator for a number of art events with international artists (the "Sigalit Landau's
- Video retrospective" exhibition with the Israel Embassy support; open-air
  "Jaquar summer
- Museum" exhibition with the Jaguar brand support and exhibition "Bond by GQ" with the GQ
- Brand contribution) (2012).